{
	"description": "Kanji for 日本漢字能力検定 1級",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "一掬", "answers": [ "いっきく" ], "comment": "small amount" },
	{ "question": "万斛", "answers": [ "ばんこく" ], "comment": "copious (tears)" },
	{ "question": "丱角", "answers": [ "かんかく" ] },
	{ "question": "乖背", "answers": [ "かいはい" ] },
	{ "question": "乖離", "answers": [ "かいり" ], "comment": "divergence; alienation; deviation; estrangement; separation; detachment" },
	{ "question": "乞丐", "answers": [ "きっかい" ], "comment": "beggar; bum" },
	{ "question": "仄聞", "answers": [ "そくぶん" ], "comment": "hearing casually; hearing by chance; learning by hearsay" },
	{ "question": "仇讐", "answers": [ "きゅうしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "仏龕", "answers": [ "ぶつがん" ] },
	{ "question": "伉儷", "answers": [ "こうれい" ], "comment": "married couple; spouses; husband and wife" },
	{ "question": "佚遊", "answers": [ "いつゆう" ] },
	{ "question": "佶屈", "answers": [ "きっくつ" ] },
	{ "question": "俊髦", "answers": [ "しゅんぼう" ] },
	{ "question": "倚藉", "answers": [ "いしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "倥偬", "answers": [ "こうそう" ], "comment": "hurrying" },
	{ "question": "偃月", "answers": [ "えんげつ" ], "comment": "crescent moon" },
	{ "question": "偃蹇", "answers": [ "えんけん" ] },
	{ "question": "僭称", "answers": [ "せんしょう" ], "comment": "pretension; assumption (of a title)" },
	{ "question": "僭越", "answers": [ "せんえつ" ], "comment": "presumptuous; arrogant; audacious; forward; insolent" },
	{ "question": "兌換", "answers": [ "だかん" ], "comment": "conversion (of paper money, esp. into specie)" },
	{ "question": "冕旒", "answers": [ "べんりゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "冪冪", "answers": [ "べきべき" ], "comment": "billowing (clouds, dust)" },
	{ "question": "冪法", "answers": [ "べきほう" ] },
	{ "question": "刈穫", "answers": [ "がいかく" ] },
	{ "question": "刪修", "answers": [ "さんしゅう" ], "comment": "revision; reform" },
	{ "question": "剔抉", "answers": [ "てっけつ" ], "comment": "gouging (out); exposure" },
	{ "question": "剪定", "answers": [ "せんてい" ], "comment": "pruning" },
	{ "question": "剪裁", "answers": [ "せんさい" ], "comment": "cutting; trimming; shearing; pruning" },
	{ "question": "剪除", "answers": [ "せんじょ" ], "comment": "cutting off; cut(ting) out" },
	{ "question": "剽悍", "answers": [ "ひょうかん" ], "comment": "fierceness; daring" },
	{ "question": "剽疾", "answers": [ "ひょうしつ" ] },
	{ "question": "剽窃", "answers": [ "ひょうせつ" ], "comment": "plagiarism; piracy" },
	{ "question": "勿怪", "answers": [ "もっけ" ], "comment": "unexpected" },
	{ "question": "勿論", "answers": [ "もちろん" ], "comment": "of course; certainly; naturally" },
	{ "question": "匍匐", "answers": [ "ほふく" ], "comment": "creeping; crawling; sneaking" },
	{ "question": "千仞", "answers": [ "せんじん" ], "comment": "great depth; bottomless\ngreat height" },
	{ "question": "午餉", "answers": [ "ごしょう" ] },
	{ "question": "反噬", "answers": [ "はんぜい" ], "comment": "turning against one's master; returning evil for good" },
	{ "question": "叮嚀", "answers": [ "ていねい" ], "comment": "polite; courteous; civil\ncareful; close; thorough; conscientious" },
	{ "question": "吶喊", "answers": [ "とっかん" ], "comment": "battlecry; cheer; cry where one breathes in a large volume of air and then releases it suddenly in a loud cry\nrushing at the enemy" },
	{ "question": "呑噬", "answers": [ "どんぜい" ] },
	{ "question": "呻吟", "answers": [ "しんぎん" ], "comment": "moaning; groaning" },
	{ "question": "咄嗟", "answers": [ "とっさ" ], "comment": "moment; instant" },
	{ "question": "咆哮", "answers": [ "ほうこう" ], "comment": "yell; roar; howl" },
	{ "question": "咨詢", "answers": [ "しじゅん" ], "comment": "question; enquiry; inquiry; consultation; advice-seeking" },
	{ "question": "咫尺", "answers": [ "しせき" ], "comment": "very short distance" },
	{ "question": "啖呵", "answers": [ "たんか" ], "comment": "caustic words" },
	{ "question": "喇叭", "answers": [ "らっぱ" ], "comment": "trumpet; horn; bugle" },
	{ "question": "喘息", "answers": [ "ぜんそく" ], "comment": "asthma; phthisis" },
	{ "question": "喘鳴", "answers": [ "ぜんめい" ], "comment": "stridor; wheezing; noisy breathing" },
	{ "question": "喚鐘", "answers": [ "かんしょう" ] },
	{ "question": "嗜眠", "answers": [ "しみん" ], "comment": "deep sleep; torpor" },
	{ "question": "嗜虐", "answers": [ "しぎゃく" ], "comment": "sadism" },
	{ "question": "嘲弄", "answers": [ "ちょうろう" ], "comment": "scorn; mockery; ridicule" },
	{ "question": "嘲戯", "answers": [ "ちょうぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "嘲罵", "answers": [ "ちょうば" ], "comment": "taunt; insult; abuse" },
	{ "question": "器皿", "answers": [ "きべい" ] },
	{ "question": "嚠喨", "answers": [ "りゅうりょう" ], "comment": "clear and resounding (as a voice or musical instrument)" },
	{ "question": "囃子", "answers": [ "はやし" ], "comment": "accompaniment for traditional performances (noh, kabuki, etc.); orchestra; band" },
	{ "question": "四裔", "answers": [ "しえい" ] },
	{ "question": "圏套", "answers": [ "けんとう" ] },
	{ "question": "圧状", "answers": [ "おうじょう" ], "comment": "document written under duress\ncoercion" },
	{ "question": "埴輪", "answers": [ "はにわ" ], "comment": "haniwa; hollow unglazed terracotta figures from the Kofun period" },
	{ "question": "堰堤", "answers": [ "えんてい" ], "comment": "dam; weir" },
	{ "question": "塵埃", "answers": [ "じんあい" ], "comment": "dust; dirt; this drab world" },
	{ "question": "墳塋", "answers": [ "ふんえい" ] },
	{ "question": "壅塞", "answers": [ "ようそく" ] },
	{ "question": "夭折", "answers": [ "ようせつ" ], "comment": "premature death" },
	{ "question": "夭逝", "answers": [ "ようせい" ], "comment": "premature death" },
	{ "question": "夾雑", "answers": [ "きょうざつ" ] },
	{ "question": "套言", "answers": [ "とうげん" ] },
	{ "question": "奢侈", "answers": [ "しゃし" ], "comment": "luxury; extravagance" },
	{ "question": "奢靡", "answers": [ "しゃび" ] },
	{ "question": "委悉", "answers": [ "いしつ" ] },
	{ "question": "婀娜", "answers": [ "あだ" ], "comment": "coquettish woman" },
	{ "question": "婚娶", "answers": [ "こんしゅ" ] },
	{ "question": "婢僕", "answers": [ "ひぼく" ] },
	{ "question": "嫩緑", "answers": [ "どんりょく" ] },
	{ "question": "嫩草", "answers": [ "どんそう" ] },
	{ "question": "嬌羞", "answers": [ "きょうしゅう" ], "comment": "charming and coy" },
	{ "question": "嬌艶", "answers": [ "きょうえん" ] },
	{ "question": "孵化", "answers": [ "ふか" ], "comment": "incubation; hatching" },
	{ "question": "安佚", "answers": [ "あんいつ" ], "comment": "(idle) ease; idleness; indolence" },
	{ "question": "宏闊", "answers": [ "こうかつ" ], "comment": "spaciousness; extensiveness; expansiveness; vastness" },
	{ "question": "宸筆", "answers": [ "しんぴつ" ] },
	{ "question": "寐語", "answers": [ "びご" ], "comment": "sleep-talking; nonsense" },
	{ "question": "寥落", "answers": [ "りょうらく" ] },
	{ "question": "寵辱", "answers": [ "ちょうじょく" ] },
	{ "question": "屛居", "answers": [ "へいきょ" ], "comment": "living in retirement" },
	{ "question": "岌岌", "answers": [ "きゅうきゅう" ], "comment": "tall (as a mountain, etc.)\nexceedingly dangerous" },
	{ "question": "島嶼", "answers": [ "とうしょ" ], "comment": "islands" },
	{ "question": "峻別", "answers": [ "しゅんべつ" ], "comment": "rigorous distinction" },
	{ "question": "嶄然", "answers": [ "ざんぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "嶮路", "answers": [ "けんろ" ], "comment": "steep path" },
	{ "question": "巨擘", "answers": [ "きょはく" ], "comment": "authority; big-shot; star" },
	{ "question": "巫覡", "answers": [ "ふげき" ], "comment": "shaman; oracle; diviner; medium" },
	{ "question": "帑幣", "answers": [ "どへい" ] },
	{ "question": "帛書", "answers": [ "はくしょ" ] },
	{ "question": "帥先", "answers": [ "そっせん" ], "comment": "taking the initiative" },
	{ "question": "帷幔", "answers": [ "いまん" ] },
	{ "question": "庖丁", "answers": [ "ほうちょう" ], "comment": "kitchen knife; carving knife\ncooking; food" },
	{ "question": "弊竇", "answers": [ "へいとう" ] },
	{ "question": "弛張", "answers": [ "しちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "弛緩", "answers": [ "しかん" ], "comment": "relaxation (e.g. of muscles); becoming flaccid" },
	{ "question": "彎月", "answers": [ "わんげつ" ], "comment": "crescent" },
	{ "question": "彷彿", "answers": [ "ほうふつ" ], "comment": "close resemblance; vivid reminder (e.g. of the past)" },
	{ "question": "彷徨", "answers": [ "ほうこう" ], "comment": "wandering; rambling; roaming" },
	{ "question": "忸怩", "answers": [ "じくじ" ], "comment": "bashful; shameful; ashamed" },
	{ "question": "怙恃", "answers": [ "こじ" ] },
	{ "question": "怱忙", "answers": [ "そうぼう" ] },
	{ "question": "恐懼", "answers": [ "きょうく" ], "comment": "being struck with awe" },
	{ "question": "恬安", "answers": [ "てんあん" ] },
	{ "question": "悃誠", "answers": [ "こんせい" ] },
	{ "question": "悃願", "answers": [ "こんがん" ] },
	{ "question": "愁悶", "answers": [ "しゅうもん" ] },
	{ "question": "慊焉", "answers": [ "けんえん" ] },
	{ "question": "慓悍", "answers": [ "ひょうかん" ] },
	{ "question": "慟哭", "answers": [ "どうこく" ], "comment": "wailing; lamentation" },
	{ "question": "慫慂", "answers": [ "しょうよう" ], "comment": "advice; recommendation; suggestion; inducement; persuasion" },
	{ "question": "慳吝", "answers": [ "けんりん" ] },
	{ "question": "慳貪", "answers": [ "けんどん" ] },
	{ "question": "憐惜", "answers": [ "れんせき" ] },
	{ "question": "憫諒", "answers": [ "びんりょう" ], "comment": "pity; compassion; sympathizing" },
	{ "question": "懊悩", "answers": [ "おうのう" ], "comment": "anguish; trouble; agony" },
	{ "question": "懐孕", "answers": [ "かいよう" ] },
	{ "question": "懦夫", "answers": [ "だふ" ] },
	{ "question": "懦弱", "answers": [ "だじゃく" ], "comment": "apathetic; lackadaisical; spiritless; gutless; weak-willed; unenterprising; enervated; effete\nphysically weak; feeble; effeminate" },
	{ "question": "懾伏", "answers": [ "しょうふく" ], "comment": "prostrating oneself in fear; kneeling in fear; crouching in fear; prostration" },
	{ "question": "懿徳", "answers": [ "いとく" ] },
	{ "question": "戌亥", "answers": [ "いぬい" ], "comment": "northwest" },
	{ "question": "戒飭", "answers": [ "かいちょく" ], "comment": "admonishment; warning" },
	{ "question": "戡定", "answers": [ "かんてい" ] },
	{ "question": "截然", "answers": [ "せつぜん" ], "comment": "clear; sharp; distinct; distinctive" },
	{ "question": "扞格", "answers": [ "かんかく" ], "comment": "mutual incompatibility; mutual rejection" },
	{ "question": "扼腕", "answers": [ "やくわん" ] },
	{ "question": "抃舞", "answers": [ "べんぶ" ], "comment": "dancing and clapping one's hands with joy" },
	{ "question": "抉剔", "answers": [ "けってき" ] },
	{ "question": "抒情", "answers": [ "じょじょう" ], "comment": "lyricism; description or expression of one's feelings" },
	{ "question": "抛擲", "answers": [ "ほうてき" ], "comment": "abandoning; giving up; quitting" },
	{ "question": "抛棄", "answers": [ "ほうき" ], "comment": "abandonment; renunciation; resignation; abdication (responsibility, right)" },
	{ "question": "拇印", "answers": [ "ぼいん" ], "comment": "thumb print" },
	{ "question": "拈出", "answers": [ "ねんしゅつ" ], "comment": "contriving (to raise funds, to find time, etc.)\nworking out (a solution)" },
	{ "question": "拘繋", "answers": [ "こうけい" ] },
	{ "question": "捍格", "answers": [ "かんかく" ], "comment": "mutual incompatibility; mutual rejection" },
	{ "question": "掎角", "answers": [ "きかく" ] },
	{ "question": "推輓", "answers": [ "すいばん" ] },
	{ "question": "揶揄", "answers": [ "やゆ" ], "comment": "banter; raillery; tease; ridicule; banter with" },
	{ "question": "搗精", "answers": [ "とうせい" ], "comment": "rice polishing (removing the shell of brown rice to leave white rice)" },
	{ "question": "擣衣", "answers": [ "とうい" ] },
	{ "question": "放曠", "answers": [ "ほうこう" ] },
	{ "question": "救恤", "answers": [ "きゅうじゅつ" ] },
	{ "question": "斂葬", "answers": [ "れんそう" ], "comment": "interment; burial" },
	{ "question": "斧鑿", "answers": [ "ふさく" ], "comment": "lucubration; elaboration; chisel and ax" },
	{ "question": "断截", "answers": [ "だんせつ" ], "comment": "cutting; cutting off; severing" },
	{ "question": "旌表", "answers": [ "せいひょう" ] },
	{ "question": "明礬", "answers": [ "みょうばん" ], "comment": "alum" },
	{ "question": "曩昔", "answers": [ "のうせき" ] },
	{ "question": "朦朧", "answers": [ "もうろう" ], "comment": "dim; hazy; vague; indistinct; ambiguous; faint; obscure" },
	{ "question": "杞憂", "answers": [ "きゆう" ], "comment": "absurd fear; needless anxiety" },
	{ "question": "束脩", "answers": [ "そくしゅう" ], "comment": "entrance fee; initiation fee; registration fee; present to a teacher\ngift of dried meat from a new vassal or pupil" },
	{ "question": "杪春", "answers": [ "びょうしゅん" ], "comment": "end of spring" },
	{ "question": "枳棘", "answers": [ "ききょく" ] },
	{ "question": "桎梏", "answers": [ "しっこく" ], "comment": "bonds; fetters" },
	{ "question": "梵唄", "answers": [ "ぼんばい" ], "comment": "song in praise of Buddhas virtues" },
	{ "question": "梵鐘", "answers": [ "ぼんしょう" ], "comment": "bonshō; Buddhist temple bell" },
	{ "question": "検覈", "answers": [ "けんかく" ] },
	{ "question": "楔状", "answers": [ "けつじょう" ], "comment": "wedge-shaped; cuneate; cuneiform" },
	{ "question": "欷歔", "answers": [ "ききょ" ] },
	{ "question": "歎美", "answers": [ "たんび" ], "comment": "admiration; adoration; extolling" },
	{ "question": "歿年", "answers": [ "ぼつねん" ], "comment": "year of a person's death\none's age at death" },
	{ "question": "殄滅", "answers": [ "てんめつ" ], "comment": "complete and utter annihilation" },
	{ "question": "毀傷", "answers": [ "きしょう" ], "comment": "injury; damage" },
	{ "question": "毫末", "answers": [ "ごうまつ" ], "comment": "minute amount" },
	{ "question": "毫毛", "answers": [ "ごうもう" ] },
	{ "question": "毫髪", "answers": [ "ごうはつ" ] },
	{ "question": "沐雨", "answers": [ "もくう" ] },
	{ "question": "泛論", "answers": [ "はんろん" ] },
	{ "question": "波濤", "answers": [ "はとう" ], "comment": "surging sea; rough sea; large waves" },
	{ "question": "流眄", "answers": [ "りゅうべん" ] },
	{ "question": "浅葱", "answers": [ "あさぎ" ], "comment": "pale blue-green\nchive (edible plant, Allium schoenoprasum)" },
	{ "question": "涕洟", "answers": [ "ていい" ] },
	{ "question": "涵養", "answers": [ "かんよう" ], "comment": "cultivation (esp. character, virtue, moral sentiment); fostering; training\npenetration (e.g. surface water into an aquifer); recharging (of groundwater)" },
	{ "question": "淫風", "answers": [ "いんぷう" ], "comment": "lewd manners; immorality" },
	{ "question": "滔天", "answers": [ "とうてん" ] },
	{ "question": "潸然", "answers": [ "さんぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "澆漓", "answers": [ "ぎょうり" ] },
	{ "question": "澆薄", "answers": [ "ぎょうはく" ] },
	{ "question": "澗泉", "answers": [ "かんせん" ] },
	{ "question": "澹乎", "answers": [ "たんこ" ] },
	{ "question": "瀉下", "answers": [ "しゃか" ], "comment": "catharsis; purgation; evacuation; purging the bowels; diarrhea\npouring out (water, etc.)" },
	{ "question": "瀉出", "answers": [ "しゃしゅつ" ] },
	{ "question": "瀑布", "answers": [ "ばくふ" ], "comment": "waterfall; cataract; cascade" },
	{ "question": "灌注", "answers": [ "かんちゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "灑掃", "answers": [ "さいそう" ] },
	{ "question": "炯然", "answers": [ "けいぜん" ], "comment": "shining; radiant; bright" },
	{ "question": "炯眼", "answers": [ "けいがん" ], "comment": "penetrating eyes; insightfulness" },
	{ "question": "烏鵲", "answers": [ "うじゃく" ] },
	{ "question": "煢然", "answers": [ "けいぜん" ], "comment": "alone; helpless" },
	{ "question": "煢煢", "answers": [ "けいけい" ] },
	{ "question": "煤煙", "answers": [ "ばいえん" ], "comment": "dirty smoke; soot and smoke" },
	{ "question": "煩悶", "answers": [ "はんもん" ], "comment": "worry; agony" },
	{ "question": "燧火", "answers": [ "すいか" ] },
	{ "question": "燧烽", "answers": [ "すいほう" ] },
	{ "question": "燼灰", "answers": [ "じんかい" ] },
	{ "question": "爛漫", "answers": [ "らんまん" ], "comment": "glorious; luxuriant; splendid; in full bloom; in full glory" },
	{ "question": "爛然", "answers": [ "らんぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "爛熟", "answers": [ "らんじゅく" ], "comment": "overripeness; full maturity (of); overmaturity" },
	{ "question": "爛発", "answers": [ "らんぱつ" ] },
	{ "question": "爛脱", "answers": [ "らんだつ" ] },
	{ "question": "爬掻", "answers": [ "はそう" ] },
	{ "question": "牙籌", "answers": [ "がちゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "犇犇", "answers": [ "ひしひし" ], "comment": "acutely; severely; tightly; keenly" },
	{ "question": "狡黠", "answers": [ "こうかつ" ] },
	{ "question": "猩紅", "answers": [ "しょうこう" ] },
	{ "question": "瑕釁", "answers": [ "かきん" ], "comment": "scratch; chip; nick\nflaw; fault; defect\nshame; disgrace" },
	{ "question": "瑟瑟", "answers": [ "しつしつ" ] },
	{ "question": "瑣細", "answers": [ "ささい" ] },
	{ "question": "瑰麗", "answers": [ "かいれい" ] },
	{ "question": "瓦礫", "answers": [ "がれき" ], "comment": "rubble; debris; wreckage" },
	{ "question": "甄別", "answers": [ "けんべつ" ] },
	{ "question": "甲冑", "answers": [ "かっちゅう" ], "comment": "armor and helmet (armour)" },
	{ "question": "畿甸", "answers": [ "きでん" ] },
	{ "question": "疆域", "answers": [ "きょういき" ], "comment": "boundary; border; precinct; grounds" },
	{ "question": "疆界", "answers": [ "きょうかい" ] },
	{ "question": "痙攣", "answers": [ "けいれん" ], "comment": "convulsion; cramp; spasm; twitch; fit" },
	{ "question": "瘠地", "answers": [ "せきち" ], "comment": "barren land; arid soil" },
	{ "question": "瘢痕", "answers": [ "はんこん" ], "comment": "scar; cicatrix" },
	{ "question": "癘気", "answers": [ "れいき" ] },
	{ "question": "癰疽", "answers": [ "ようそ" ], "comment": "any serious skin eruption" },
	{ "question": "癲癇", "answers": [ "てんかん" ], "comment": "epilepsy; epileptic fit" },
	{ "question": "白皙", "answers": [ "はくせき" ], "comment": "white" },
	{ "question": "盥漱", "answers": [ "かんそう" ], "comment": "washing one's hands and rinsing one's mouth" },
	{ "question": "直截", "answers": [ "ちょくせつ" ], "comment": "direct; frank; straightforward; plain\ndecisive; prompt" },
	{ "question": "眩惑", "answers": [ "げんわく" ], "comment": "dazzling; blinding" },
	{ "question": "眩暈", "answers": [ "げんうん" ], "comment": "dizziness; giddiness; vertigo" },
	{ "question": "眷顧", "answers": [ "けんこ" ], "comment": "favor; patronage; being partial to; paying special attention to" },
	{ "question": "睥睨", "answers": [ "へいげい" ], "comment": "glaring at; lording over" },
	{ "question": "瞞着", "answers": [ "まんちゃく" ], "comment": "deception; cheating; trickery; fraud" },
	{ "question": "知悉", "answers": [ "ちしつ" ], "comment": "complete knowledge" },
	{ "question": "矮躯", "answers": [ "わいく" ], "comment": "small stature" },
	{ "question": "石鏃", "answers": [ "せきぞく" ], "comment": "flint arrowhead" },
	{ "question": "石鹸", "answers": [ "せっけん" ], "comment": "soap" },
	{ "question": "硯箱", "answers": [ "すずりばこ" ], "comment": "inkstone case" },
	{ "question": "社稷", "answers": [ "しゃしょく" ], "comment": "state; country; nation\ntutelary deity; god of grain" },
	{ "question": "神饌", "answers": [ "しんせん" ], "comment": "food and alcohol offering to the gods" },
	{ "question": "禰宜", "answers": [ "ねぎ" ], "comment": "senior priest (of a Shinto shrine, below chief priest and deputy chief priest)\ngrasshopper; locust" },
	{ "question": "秉燭", "answers": [ "へいしょく", "ひょうそく", "ひんそく" ] },
	{ "question": "稼穡", "answers": [ "かしょく" ], "comment": "planting and harvesting; farming" },
	{ "question": "穢身", "answers": [ "えしん" ] },
	{ "question": "空翠", "answers": [ "くうすい" ] },
	{ "question": "窈然", "answers": [ "ようぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "窈窕", "answers": [ "ようちょう" ], "comment": "graceful; slim and beautiful" },
	{ "question": "窮愁", "answers": [ "きゅうしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "竦然", "answers": [ "しょうぜん" ], "comment": "terrified; horrified" },
	{ "question": "竿檣", "answers": [ "かんしょう" ] },
	{ "question": "笞撻", "answers": [ "ちたつ" ] },
	{ "question": "筮竹", "answers": [ "ぜいちく" ], "comment": "bamboo divination stick" },
	{ "question": "箝制", "answers": [ "かんせい" ] },
	{ "question": "箭眼", "answers": [ "せんがん" ] },
	{ "question": "篋底", "answers": [ "きょうてい" ], "comment": "bottom of a box" },
	{ "question": "篩骨", "answers": [ "しこつ" ], "comment": "ethmoid bone (of the skull)" },
	{ "question": "簫鼓", "answers": [ "しょうこ" ] },
	{ "question": "簷滴", "answers": [ "えんてき" ] },
	{ "question": "籀文", "answers": [ "ちゅうぶん" ], "comment": "large seal script (dating from China's Spring and Autumn period onward)" },
	{ "question": "紆余", "answers": [ "うよ" ], "comment": "meandering; beating around the bush; abundant talent" },
	{ "question": "紆曲", "answers": [ "うきょく" ], "comment": "meandering; winding" },
	{ "question": "絮説", "answers": [ "じょせつ" ] },
	{ "question": "綏撫", "answers": [ "すいぶ" ], "comment": "lulled into peacefulness; comforted and consoled" },
	{ "question": "綟網", "answers": [ "もじあみ" ] },
	{ "question": "綢繆", "answers": [ "ちゅうびゅう" ], "comment": "coiled about; entangled; entwined\nfamiliar; harmonious" },
	{ "question": "綽然", "answers": [ "しゃくぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "綾羅", "answers": [ "りょうら" ], "comment": "elaborated cloth; figured silk and thin silk" },
	{ "question": "縹色", "answers": [ "はなだいろ" ], "comment": "light indigo" },
	{ "question": "羈紲", "answers": [ "きせつ" ] },
	{ "question": "羈絆", "answers": [ "きはん" ], "comment": "fetters; shackles; restraints; bond; connection" },
	{ "question": "羶血", "answers": [ "せんけつ" ], "comment": "stink of blood or meat; meat eating barbarian (i.e. Westerner)" },
	{ "question": "羸弱", "answers": [ "るいじゃく" ], "comment": "weakness; feebleness; imbecility" },
	{ "question": "翅鳥", "answers": [ "しちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "翹望", "answers": [ "ぎょうぼう" ], "comment": "looking forward (to something); awaiting" },
	{ "question": "翹楚", "answers": [ "ぎょうそ" ] },
	{ "question": "耄耋", "answers": [ "ぼうてつ" ] },
	{ "question": "耽美", "answers": [ "たんび" ], "comment": "aesthetics" },
	{ "question": "聊爾", "answers": [ "りょうじ" ] },
	{ "question": "聊頼", "answers": [ "りょうらい" ] },
	{ "question": "聘問", "answers": [ "へいもん" ] },
	{ "question": "聚斂", "answers": [ "しゅうれん" ], "comment": "(levying of a) heavy taxation" },
	{ "question": "聯想", "answers": [ "れんそう" ], "comment": "association (of ideas); being reminded (of something); suggestion" },
	{ "question": "聾唖", "answers": [ "ろうあ" ], "comment": "deafness\ndeaf-mute" },
	{ "question": "肯綮", "answers": [ "こうけい" ], "comment": "the essential point" },
	{ "question": "胡乱", "answers": [ "うろん" ], "comment": "suspicious looking; fishy" },
	{ "question": "脛骨", "answers": [ "けいこつ" ], "comment": "tibia; shinbone" },
	{ "question": "膂力", "answers": [ "りょりょく" ], "comment": "physical strength; the strength of one's muscles" },
	{ "question": "膺懲", "answers": [ "ようちょう" ], "comment": "punishment; chastisement" },
	{ "question": "膾炙", "answers": [ "かいしゃ" ], "comment": "household word; universal praise" },
	{ "question": "臚列", "answers": [ "ろれつ" ], "comment": "lined up in a row" },
	{ "question": "舐犢", "answers": [ "しとく" ] },
	{ "question": "舟楫", "answers": [ "しゅうしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "舳艫", "answers": [ "じくろ" ] },
	{ "question": "艟艨", "answers": [ "どうもう" ] },
	{ "question": "芥蔕", "answers": [ "かいたい" ] },
	{ "question": "花瞼", "answers": [ "かけん" ], "comment": "beautiful eyelids" },
	{ "question": "英邁", "answers": [ "えいまい" ], "comment": "wise and great" },
	{ "question": "茗園", "answers": [ "めいえん" ] },
	{ "question": "茣蓙", "answers": [ "ござ" ], "comment": "rush mat; matting; mat" },
	{ "question": "茫洋", "answers": [ "ぼうよう" ], "comment": "vastness" },
	{ "question": "茱萸", "answers": [ "ぐみ" ], "comment": "oleaster (any plant of genus Elaeagnus); silverberry (US)" },
	{ "question": "荏苒", "answers": [ "じんぜん" ], "comment": "procrastination" },
	{ "question": "菲徳", "answers": [ "ひとく" ] },
	{ "question": "菲才", "answers": [ "ひさい" ], "comment": "lack of ability; incompetence; incapacity" },
	{ "question": "萍水", "answers": [ "へいすい" ] },
	{ "question": "葷菜", "answers": [ "くんさい" ] },
	{ "question": "蒐集", "answers": [ "しゅうしゅう" ], "comment": "gathering up; collection; accumulation" },
	{ "question": "薙髪", "answers": [ "ちはつ" ] },
	{ "question": "藜羹", "answers": [ "れいこう" ] },
	{ "question": "藹藹", "answers": [ "あいあい" ], "comment": "harmonious; peaceful; congenial\nluxuriant (vegetation)" },
	{ "question": "蘊蓄", "answers": [ "うんちく" ], "comment": "great erudition; extensive knowledge; one's vast stock of knowledge" },
	{ "question": "蘊藉", "answers": [ "うんしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "虧盈", "answers": [ "きえい" ], "comment": "waning and waxing (usu. of the moon)" },
	{ "question": "蛹化", "answers": [ "ようか" ], "comment": "pupation" },
	{ "question": "蛹虫", "answers": [ "ようちゅう" ], "comment": "pupa; chrysalis" },
	{ "question": "蜑戸", "answers": [ "たんこ" ] },
	{ "question": "蝉蛻", "answers": [ "せんぜい" ] },
	{ "question": "蝴蝶", "answers": [ "こちょう" ], "comment": "butterfly" },
	{ "question": "蟄伏", "answers": [ "ちっぷく" ], "comment": "hibernation; staying home or in place" },
	{ "question": "蟄居", "answers": [ "ちっきょ" ], "comment": "keeping house; being confined to one's house" },
	{ "question": "蟠屈", "answers": [ "ばんくつ" ] },
	{ "question": "蟠踞", "answers": [ "ばんきょ" ], "comment": "becoming firmly established; putting down strong roots\nexercising authority; being dominant; holding sway\nsettling in a coiled shape" },
	{ "question": "蠱惑", "answers": [ "こわく" ], "comment": "fascination; glamour; glamor; enchantment; seduction" },
	{ "question": "蠹害", "answers": [ "とがい" ] },
	{ "question": "蠹毒", "answers": [ "とどく" ] },
	{ "question": "衍義", "answers": [ "えんぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "街衢", "answers": [ "がいく" ], "comment": "town" },
	{ "question": "袂別", "answers": [ "べいべつ" ] },
	{ "question": "袒裼", "answers": [ "たんせき" ] },
	{ "question": "褫奪", "answers": [ "ちだつ" ] },
	{ "question": "褻言", "answers": [ "せつげん" ] },
	{ "question": "覬覦", "answers": [ "きゆ" ] },
	{ "question": "解傭", "answers": [ "かいよう" ] },
	{ "question": "訥弁", "answers": [ "とつべん" ], "comment": "slowness of speech; awkwardness of speech" },
	{ "question": "詠懐", "answers": [ "えいかい" ] },
	{ "question": "誄詞", "answers": [ "るいし" ] },
	{ "question": "誣告", "answers": [ "ぶこく" ], "comment": "false accusation; slander; calumny" },
	{ "question": "誣罔", "answers": [ "ふもう" ], "comment": "slander" },
	{ "question": "諂諛", "answers": [ "てんゆ" ] },
	{ "question": "諛言", "answers": [ "ゆげん" ] },
	{ "question": "諠譁", "answers": [ "けんか" ], "comment": "quarrel; brawl; fight; squabble; scuffle; argument" },
	{ "question": "諠鬧", "answers": [ "けんとう" ] },
	{ "question": "諡号", "answers": [ "しごう" ], "comment": "posthumous name (based the deeds one has performed in their lifetime)\nposthumous Buddhist name" },
	{ "question": "謗毀", "answers": [ "ぼうき" ] },
	{ "question": "謫居", "answers": [ "たっきょ" ] },
	{ "question": "謬見", "answers": [ "びゅうけん" ], "comment": "fallacy" },
	{ "question": "謬説", "answers": [ "びゅうせつ" ], "comment": "fallacy; fallacious argument" },
	{ "question": "謹飭", "answers": [ "きんちょく" ], "comment": "deep modesty; deep discretion" },
	{ "question": "譎詐", "answers": [ "けっさ" ], "comment": "falsehood; fabrication; dissimulation" },
	{ "question": "譴責", "answers": [ "けんせき" ], "comment": "reprimand; rebuke; censure; reproof" },
	{ "question": "貶謫", "answers": [ "へんたく" ] },
	{ "question": "贅肬", "answers": [ "ぜいゆう" ] },
	{ "question": "贅言", "answers": [ "ぜいげん" ], "comment": "verbosity; redundancy" },
	{ "question": "贍給", "answers": [ "せんきゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "赫灼", "answers": [ "かくしゃく" ] },
	{ "question": "赭顔", "answers": [ "しゃがん" ], "comment": "ruddy face" },
	{ "question": "跋扈", "answers": [ "ばっこ" ], "comment": "rampancy; prevalence; domination" },
	{ "question": "跋文", "answers": [ "ばつぶん" ], "comment": "afterword" },
	{ "question": "跋渉", "answers": [ "ばっしょう" ], "comment": "wandering" },
	{ "question": "跣足", "answers": [ "せんそく" ], "comment": "barefoot\nsuperior to (a professional, etc. in ability or achievement)" },
	{ "question": "踉蹌", "answers": [ "ろうそう" ] },
	{ "question": "蹂躙", "answers": [ "じゅうりん" ], "comment": "trampling down; overrunning; infringement; violation" },
	{ "question": "蹈襲", "answers": [ "とうしゅう" ], "comment": "following (e.g. suit, in someone's footsteps, etc.); emulation" },
	{ "question": "蹣跚", "answers": [ "まんさん" ] },
	{ "question": "車站", "answers": [ "しゃたん" ] },
	{ "question": "軋轢", "answers": [ "あつれき" ], "comment": "friction; discord; strife" },
	{ "question": "軒輊", "answers": [ "けんち" ], "comment": "high and low; disparity" },
	{ "question": "軼事", "answers": [ "いつじ" ] },
	{ "question": "輓近", "answers": [ "ばんきん" ], "comment": "lately; recently" },
	{ "question": "輜重", "answers": [ "しちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "輻射", "answers": [ "ふくしゃ" ], "comment": "radiation" },
	{ "question": "輻輳", "answers": [ "ふくそう" ], "comment": "congestion (e.g. traffic); overcrowding\nconvergence (esp. optical)" },
	{ "question": "進陟", "answers": [ "しんちょく" ], "comment": "progress; being under way" },
	{ "question": "逼迫", "answers": [ "ひっぱく" ], "comment": "stringency (financial); (monetary) tightness\nimpending (dangers); pressing (crisis)" },
	{ "question": "遁走", "answers": [ "とんそう" ], "comment": "fleeing; escape" },
	{ "question": "遯月", "answers": [ "とんげつ" ] },
	{ "question": "邁往", "answers": [ "まいおう" ] },
	{ "question": "邁進", "answers": [ "まいしん" ], "comment": "pushing forward (undaunted, bravely); working vigorously towards an aim; struggling on; striving towards" },
	{ "question": "邏卒", "answers": [ "らそつ" ], "comment": "serviceman on patrol\npoliceman (early Meiji era)" },
	{ "question": "鄙見", "answers": [ "ひけん" ], "comment": "my humble opinion" },
	{ "question": "鄙陋", "answers": [ "ひろう" ] },
	{ "question": "酋長", "answers": [ "しゅうちょう" ], "comment": "chieftain" },
	{ "question": "酥油", "answers": [ "そゆ" ] },
	{ "question": "鈑金", "answers": [ "ばんきん" ], "comment": "sheet metal; metal plate" },
	{ "question": "鑰匙", "answers": [ "やくし" ] },
	{ "question": "門閾", "answers": [ "もんいき" ] },
	{ "question": "間隙", "answers": [ "かんげき" ], "comment": "gap" },
	{ "question": "関鑰", "answers": [ "かんやく" ] },
	{ "question": "関雎", "answers": [ "かんしょ" ] },
	{ "question": "閨閤", "answers": [ "けいこう" ], "comment": "sleeping quarters; bedroom\nwoman's living room; woman" },
	{ "question": "閭門", "answers": [ "りょもん" ], "comment": "gate of a village" },
	{ "question": "闃然", "answers": [ "げきぜん" ], "comment": "quiet and still; without sign of life" },
	{ "question": "闖入", "answers": [ "ちんにゅう" ], "comment": "intrusion; forced entry" },
	{ "question": "阡陌", "answers": [ "せんぱく" ] },
	{ "question": "阿諛", "answers": [ "あゆ" ], "comment": "flattery" },
	{ "question": "陬遠", "answers": [ "すうえん" ] },
	{ "question": "隧道", "answers": [ "ずいどう" ], "comment": "tunnel" },
	{ "question": "雨潦", "answers": [ "うろう" ] },
	{ "question": "雲鬢", "answers": [ "うんびん" ] },
	{ "question": "霖雨", "answers": [ "りんう" ], "comment": "long spell of rain" },
	{ "question": "靄然", "answers": [ "あいぜん" ], "comment": "hovering like mist or clouds\ngentle; calm" },
	{ "question": "靉靆", "answers": [ "あいたい" ], "comment": "trailing clouds" },
	{ "question": "面諛", "answers": [ "めんゆ" ] },
	{ "question": "鞆音", "answers": [ "ともね" ] },
	{ "question": "頌春", "answers": [ "しょうしゅん" ], "comment": "Happy New Year" },
	{ "question": "頤使", "answers": [ "いし" ], "comment": "bossing someone around; having a person under one's control" },
	{ "question": "頽勢", "answers": [ "たいせい" ], "comment": "decline; one's declining fortunes; decay" },
	{ "question": "頽廃", "answers": [ "たいはい" ], "comment": "degeneration; decadence; deterioration; laxness; corruption" },
	{ "question": "顧眄", "answers": [ "こべん" ] },
	{ "question": "顫動", "answers": [ "せんどう" ], "comment": "vibration\nto tremble; to shake" },
	{ "question": "顰蹙", "answers": [ "ひんしゅく" ], "comment": "frowning on; looking on with scorn; showing disapproval" },
	{ "question": "飛礫", "answers": [ "つぶて" ], "comment": "stone (used for throwing)" },
	{ "question": "馥郁", "answers": [ "ふくいく" ], "comment": "fragrant; sweet-smelling" },
	{ "question": "馮河", "answers": [ "ひょうが" ] },
	{ "question": "馳騁", "answers": [ "ちてい" ] },
	{ "question": "駁撃", "answers": [ "ばくげき" ], "comment": "attacking (someone's argument); arguing against; refuting; taking issue; contradicting" },
	{ "question": "駁論", "answers": [ "ばくろん" ], "comment": "refutation; confutation" },
	{ "question": "駑鈍", "answers": [ "どどん" ], "comment": "dull-witted; stupid; foolish" },
	{ "question": "駑駘", "answers": [ "どたい" ] },
	{ "question": "駘蕩", "answers": [ "たいとう" ], "comment": "large and wide\npeaceful and calm" },
	{ "question": "驍名", "answers": [ "ぎょうめい" ] },
	{ "question": "驚懼", "answers": [ "きょうく" ], "comment": "being startled" },
	{ "question": "髫齔", "answers": [ "ちょうしん" ] },
	{ "question": "魑魅", "answers": [ "ちみ" ], "comment": "mountain demon" },
	{ "question": "鴃舌", "answers": [ "げきぜつ" ], "comment": "barbarian jabbering" },
	{ "question": "鴆毒", "answers": [ "ちんどく" ] },
	{ "question": "鶉居", "answers": [ "じゅんきょ" ] },
	{ "question": "鶴唳", "answers": [ "かくれい" ] },
	{ "question": "鶸色", "answers": [ "ひわいろ" ] },
	{ "question": "鷙鳥", "answers": [ "しちょう" ] },
	{ "question": "鷸蚌", "answers": [ "いつぼう", "いっぽう" ], "comment": "a snipe and a clam; a snipe and a mussel" },
	{ "question": "鸞輿", "answers": [ "らんよ" ], "comment": "imperial conveyance" },
	{ "question": "鹵莽", "answers": [ "ろもう" ] },
	{ "question": "鹹味", "answers": [ "かんみ" ], "comment": "saltiness" },
	{ "question": "鹹湖", "answers": [ "かんこ" ], "comment": "salt lake; lagoon" },
	{ "question": "麋鹿", "answers": [ "びろく" ] },
	{ "question": "黐竿", "answers": [ "もちざお" ], "comment": "lime stick for catching insects" },
	{ "question": "黯然", "answers": [ "あんぜん" ], "comment": "dark; gloomy; black; unclear\ndoleful; discouraged; disappointed; tearful; dispirited" },
	{ "question": "黴菌", "answers": [ "ばいきん" ], "comment": "germ; germs; bacteria; mold; mould\nsomething harmful; vermin" },
	{ "question": "鼇頭", "answers": [ "ごうとう" ] },
	{ "question": "鼎坐", "answers": [ "ていざ" ], "comment": "three people sitting in a triangle" },
	{ "question": "鼎峙", "answers": [ "ていじ" ] },
	{ "question": "鼎談", "answers": [ "ていだん" ], "comment": "tripartite (three man) talk" },
	{ "question": "齟齬", "answers": [ "そご" ], "comment": "inconsistency; discord; conflict; discrepancy; contradiction; failure; frustration" }
]
}
